Al Vipers, welcome everyone into this crash course about our new 50 minute time frame entry models and strategy
If you are here, it means you have already completed the 4-hour swing trading strategy, so congratulations on reaching this next stage in your trading journey.
Now, let me be clear up front.
If you haven't fully learned and understood the 4-hour strategy, this 50-minute course won't make so much sense to you.
The 50-minute entries are built on top of what we already know from the higher timeframe strategy.
So, if you skip the head, I strongly recommend you going back first before diving in here on the 50-minute timeframe.
Alright so what's different about this course?
Well, first off, we are keeping things simple, short videos, straight to the point and focused purely on execution.
But most importantly, you'll notice that we will be abandoning a few concepts from the 4-hour course while introducing some new elements into our playbook.
For example, The four-hour curves while introducing some new elements into our playbook. For example, one major shift is that we'll no longer be using the order of block entries the way we did them before on the four-hour strategy.
But don't worry, we'll cover that exactly why and what we will use instead.
So, who is this entry model for? Who is this strategy for?
Who will use this 15-minute timeframe strategy?
This is for those traders who have some extra time to monitor the markets and want to scale in into opportunities to trade on the lower time frame while still leveraging the power of the higher time frame movements.
So, if you are looking at the four-hour time frame,
if you are training on the four-hour time frame
and you have some extra time,
it won't take that much..
It means that only one hour a day, extra time.
If you have that on your hands,
you can actually leverage yourself into lower time frame positions
with higher withdrawal ratio.
So, what is the goal?
lower time frame positions with higher risk-ro ratio.
So what is the goal?
As I told you,
catching higher risk-to reward ratio setups
while maintaining precision on the 4-hour time frame.
Meaning we will be following the 4-hour trend,
the 4-hour time frame.
And based on those 4-hour movements we will be monitoring,
we will switch down to the 15-minute timeframe
and will try to scale in into opportunities presenting there.
Meaning, based on the 4-hour movements,
which is actually capable of generating 2.5 risk-ro ratio per position
without the order blocks,
we will be able to add an extra 5 to 10 risk-related ratio per position,
which is insane.
And it only takes one extra hour of your time a day
to monitor the markets.
And there will be one more important change we will make
is that we will reduce the watch list.
We won't be long we no longer will be using 15 pairs on the watch list,
we will reduce it down.
be no longer will be using 15 pairs on the watch list,
we will reduce it down to 5 pairs first of all,
and later on, if it works,
we will be adding more and more up to like 7 or 8 pairs.
But we will start it with 5 pairs on the watchlist
because it's more than enough without correlation, without complications,
it's more than enough to generate animal of restore ratio and profit on a month-to-month basis.
And by the end of this course, you will have a refined entry system
that will allow you to take advantage of key market movements with confidence and efficiency.
So, without further ado, I believe we can just get started...