Everybody has problems, even you. But you have nice ocean, and don't feel now. But you will feel it.
We're trying to solve a problem. Don't tell us what we're going to feel. I'm not telling you because you're in no position to dictate that. Remember this: you're in no position.
To dictate what we're going to feel. We're going to feel very good. We're going to feel very good and very strong. People will feel influence.
You're right now not in a very good position. You've allowed yourself to be in a very bad position, and it's happening.
From the very beginning of the war, you're not in a good position. You don't have the cards right now.
With us, you start having cards. Right now, you don't. You're playing cards. You're playing cards.
You're gambling with the lives of millions of people. You're gambling with World War III. You're gambling with World War III.
And what you're doing is very disrespectful to the country, this country.
I've been very receptive. That's back to you. Far more than a lot of people said they should have. Have you said thank you once?
This entire meeting? No. In this entire meeting, have you said thank you? You went to Pennsylvania and campaigned for the opposition in October.
Offer some words of appreciation for the United States of America and the president who's trying to save your country.
Please, you think that if you will speak very loudly about the war, you can... He's not speaking loudly. He's not speaking loudly. Your country is in big trouble.
Wait a minute. No, no. You've done a lot of talking. Your country is in big trouble. I know. You're not winning. You're not winning this. I.
You have a damn good chance of coming out okay because of us. Mr. President, we are staying. You know, our country is staying strong.
From the very beginning of the war, we've been alone, and we are thankful. I said thanks. Yeah, you haven't been alone. In this cabinet, you haven't been alone. And nobody in this cabinet has. We gave you through this stupid president.
Three hundred and fifty billion dollars. We gave you military equipment, and your men are brave.
But they had to use our military. So what about your invitation? If you didn't have our military equipment, you invited them in. If you didn't have our military equipment, this war would have been over.
In two weeks. In three days, I heard it from Putin. In three days, this is something maybe less. In two weeks, of course, yes. It's going to be a very hard thing to do.
Business like this, I tell you. Just say thank you. Accept, accept that there, accept that there are, accept that there are disagreements.
And let's go litigate those disagreements, rather than trying to fight it out in the American media when you're wrong.
We know that you're wrong. But you see, I think it's good for the American people to see what's going on. I understand. I think it's very important. That's why I kept this going so long.
You have to be thankful. You don't have the cards. You're buried there. You're.
People are dying. You're running low on soldiers. Listen, you're running low on soldiers. It would be a damn good thing. And then you, then you tell us.
I don't want a ceasefire. I don't want a ceasefire. I want to go, and I wanted this. Look.
If you could get a ceasefire right now, I tell you, you take it, so the bullets stop flying and your men stop.
Of course, of course, we want to stop the war. But you're saying you don't want a ceasefire? I said to you, I want a ceasefire. We guarantee because you'll get a ceasefire faster than a agreement. Ask our people about ceasefire.
Fire, what they think. That wasn't with me. That wasn't with me. That was with a guy named Biden, who was not a smart person.
That was with, that was with Obama. Excuse me. That was with Obama, who gave you sheets, and I gave you javelins.
Yes. I gave you the javelins to take out all those tanks. Obama gave you sheets.
In fact, the statement is Obama gave sheets and Trump gave javelins.
You got to be more thankful.
Because let me tell you, you don't have the cards. With us, you have the cards, but without us, you don't have any cards.