Everybody has problems.
Even you.
But you have nice ocean and don't feel now.
But you will feel it in the future.
God bless.
You don't know that.
You will not have the war.
Don't tell us what we're going to feel.
We're trying to solve a problem.
I'm not telling you.
Because you're in no position to dictate that.
Remember that.
You're in no position to dictate what we're going to feel.
We're going to feel very good.
We're going to feel very good and very strong.
You're right now not in a very good position.
You've allowed yourself to be in a very bad position
and he happens to be right about it.
You're not in a good position.
You don't have the cards right now.
With us, you start having cards.
Right now, you're playing cards.
You're playing cards.
You're gambling with the lives of millions of people.
You're gambling with World War III.
And what you're doing is very disrespectful to the country, this country
that's backed you far more than a lot of people said they should have.
Have you said thank you once this entire meeting?
No, in this entire meeting
have you said thank you?
You went to Pennsylvania and campaigned for the opposition in October.
Offer some words of appreciation for the United States of America
and the president who's trying to save your country.
Please, you think that if you will speak very loudly about the war,
you can... He's not speaking loudly.
He's not speaking loudly.
Your country is in big trouble.
Can I answer?
No, no.
You've done a lot of talking.
Your country is in big trouble.
I know.
You're not winning.
You're not winning this.
You have a damn good chance of coming out okay because of us.
Mr. President, we are staying in our country,
staying strong from the very beginning of the war.
We've been alone
and we are thankful.
I said thanks in this cabinet.
You haven't been alone.
We gave you, through this stupid president, $350 billion.
We gave you military equipment.
And your men are brave
but they had to use our military.
If you didn't have our military equipment
if you didn't have our military equipment
this war would have been over in two weeks.
In three days.
I heard it from Putin.
This is something new.
Maybe less.
In two weeks.
Of course, yes.
It's going to be a very hard thing to do business like this, I tell you.
To say thank you
except that there are disagreements
and let's go litigate those disagreements
rather than trying to fight it out in the American media when you're wrong.
We know that you're wrong.
But you see, I think it's good for the American people
to see what's going on.
I think it's very important.
That's why I kept this going so long.
You have to be thankful.
You don't have the cards.
You're buried there.
Your people are dying.
You're running low on soldiers.
Listen, you're running low on soldiers.
It would be a damn good thing.
Then you tell us
I don't want to cease fire.
I want to go
and I wanted this.
Look.
If you could get a ceasefire right now, I tell you
you'd take it so the bullets stop flying
and your men stop getting killed.
Of course we want to stop the war.
But you're saying you don't want a ceasefire.
But I said to you with guarantees.
I want a ceasefire because you'll get a ceasefire faster than an agreement.
Ask our people about ceasefire, what they think.
It doesn't matter for you what this means.
That wasn't with me.
That was with a guy named Biden who was not a smart person.
That was with Obama.
Excuse me.
That was with Obama who gave you sheets and I gave you javelins.
I gave you the javelins to take out all those tanks.
Obama gave you sheets.
In fact, the statement is Obama gave sheets and Trump gave javelins.
You got to be more thankful
because let me tell you
you don't have the cards.
With us, you have the cards.
But without us, you don't have any cards.